you ever heard of neural plasticity how
you can create new pathways in your mind
the sanctuary beloved is God's
neuroplasticity program where as you
learn to think through these articles of
furniture it actually changes the way
you think and you stop thinking in
beastmode and you start thinking in
christ mode are you ready to eat
let us pray over the food Heavenly
Father bless this food that you have
prepared for us may we be filled
may we be nourished may we be
strengthened in Jesus name we pray amen
tonight I want to talk to you about a
message I've entitled the image of the
Beast how many of you believe that we
are living at the end of time we are
living in the last days I want to share
something with you just to set the
foundation in the book of Exodus
chapters 1 and 2 we have the story of
Moses who has been drawn out of waters
he has been drawn out of waters in
Exodus chapter 3 Moses goes into the
wilderness where he is there for how
long 40 years
so please note he is drawn out of waters
and then goes into the wilderness for 40
I'm just gonna wait he's gonna wait man
he is drawn out of waters he goes into
the wilderness for forty years and then
he returns to do the work of delivering
his people he performs miracles amen
and when you get to Exodus 20 what
happens is he establishes the covenant
amen and then something interesting
happens in Exodus chapter 24 and that's
it is 24 the Bible says that Moses went
up into the mountains and the Bible says
that a cloud received him out of the
sight of the people yeah come on yeah
come on Moses goes up into the Mount and
so we know that Moses leaves behind the
children of Israel so he has gone up
into the mountains something interesting
happens because the children of Israel
expected they thought that Jesus would
say that that Moses would return sooner
than he did and so you know time passes
and they begin to think huh
it looks like Moses is not coming back
we thought he was coming back and and
our parents told us he was coming back
and their parents believed that he was
coming back but he has not returned so
check this out while Moses is up in the
Mount and the children of Israel are
below something interesting happens
because the children of Israel make an
image to a beast the other feeling they
make an image to a beast and they begin
to worship the image of the Beast and
when Moses returns he catches everyone
off guard and the question is who is on
the Lord's side beloved this is where we
are heading this is the time we are
living in when you go to the book of
Revelation you will find in Revelation
chapter 13 Revelation chapter 12 you
will find their various beasts mentioned
and the Bible tells us that these beasts
are going to go after God's people with
a vengeance and we have
to be ready not to worship the beast not
to worship the image but don't fear
because there is good news and that good
news is what I like to call the prophecy
of Daniel how many of you are aware of
the prophecy of Daniel okay you don't
even know what I'm talking about but
you're raising your hand because you're
like the prophecy of Daniel there are
many prophecies in Daniel but I'm
talking about how many of you know the
prophecy of Daniel okay now now you're
like well I don't know the prophecy of
Daniel okay listen listen in order for
us to understand V it is the main
prophecy of the Book of Daniel now you
may not have heard it like this before
but you're very familiar with it so in
order to understand the prophecy of
Daniel we're gonna have to go through
the whole book of Daniel are you ready
to go through the whole book of Daniel
tonight don't worry it'll only take us a
few minutes so let's begin with Daniel
chapter 1 in Daniel chapter 1 we have
the story of these four Hebrew boys who
are faithful to God why because they
will not eat the kings once the Kings
meat or drink his wine who was the King
Nebuchadnezzar he is king of lot Babylon
so check this out beloved and Daniel I
want sharing with you the message now
but I've got to give it to you in pieces
it's the prophecy that you're about to
receive in pieces so listen carefully in
Daniel chapter 1 we have a group of
people who avoid the wine of Babylon
Yanis music beloved listen at the end of
time there will be a people who avoid
the wine of Babylon amen
alright Daniel chapter 2 what happens in
Daniel chapter 2 remember because these
four Hebrew boys were found worthy
avoided the why the king's wine in
Daniel chapter 2 they are given the
understanding of endtime prophecy
beloved at the time of the end there
will be a people who avoid the wine of
Babylon and because
avoid the wine of Babylon they will be
the only ones found in all the kingdom
who are able to understand the prophecy
and what was the prophecy what was the
message they gave on Nebuchadnezzar the
message was simple Babylon will fall so
Daniel won there will be a people at the
end of time who avoid the wine of
Babylon as a result they will be able
they will be the ones who will have an
understanding of the prophecy and preach
that Babylon will fall now as a result
of that Babylon will set up an image are
you catching this what chapter are we in
Daniel chapter 3 very good as a result
of this Babylon will set up an image but
when Babylon does this her sins will
have reached unto heaven do you remember
in Daniel chapter 4 where that tree
representing the kingdom of Babylon
reaches unto heaven and God says yet
your sins have gone too far
check this out beloved at the end of
time there will be a people who avoid
the wine of Babylon as a result of
avoiding the wine of Babylon they will
preach the message that Babylon has
fallen Babylon in return will build an
image and command all to bow down and
worship and when they do this their sins
will have reached unto heaven and when
their sins reach unto heaven Babylon
will fall that's Daniel chapter 5 you
remember what happened to Daniel 5 yes
that's the chapter that Babylon Falls
Babylon will be declared fallen now in
Daniel chapter 6 very interesting you
have a death decree that is issued
because we cannot find anything wrong
with Daniel we must find something
regarding the law of God are you alright
you know this prophecy don't you
you just never heard it like this have
you you know it it's nothing new beloved
you understand it you know it but check
this out so let's follow on in Daniel 7
what the little horn the little horn
will have his dominion taken away
because that's what Daniel 7 says in
Daniel 8 the sanctuary will be cleansed
amen in Daniel chapter 9 listen what
happens in Daniel chapter 9 Daniel
chapter 9 is about the 70 week prophecy
which describes the close of probation
on a group of people that reject the
Messiah are you with me so watch this in
Daniel chapter 1 there will be a people
who avoid the wine of Babylon as a
result as a result of they will be the
ones that preach the message that
Babylon is fallen Babylon in return will
set up an image demanding that all bow
down and worship when they do this their
sins will have reached unto heaven and
when that happens Babylon will be
declared fallen and as a result of this
they're going to set up a death decree
that all who will not worship the Beast
should be killed but don't fear because
the little horn will have his dominion
taken away the sanctuary will be
cleansed probation will be closed on
those that reject God Daniel 11 listen
carefully the king of the north will
come to his end and Daniel 12 Michael
Michael will stand up and the dead in
Christ shall rise beloved listen to me
the entire Book of Daniel as it is
written in chronological order is a
prophecy about God's endtime people do
you not mean we get excited all alone by
myself so beloved here's a question do
you want that to be your story
absolutely we want that to be our story
but here's the thing if you want that to
be your story you have to understand
something if you want to avoid
worshiping the Beast and His image
you've got to understand something
crucial and I'm gonna invite you to come
with me to the book of Genesis chapter 1
Genesis chapter 1 and I want you to
notice with me Genesis chapter 1 and
verse 26 when you're there please say
Amen and so the Bible says and God said
let us make man in our image after our
likeness and let them have dominion over
the lord's fish of the sea and over the
wot sol of the air and over the cattle
and over all the world's earth and over
every creeping thing that creepeth upon
the earth so there are two points I want
you to get here number one man was made
in the likeness and the image of God
what does that mean what does it mean
that man was made in the likeness and
the image of God does it mean that man
looked like God or doesn't mean that man
acted had the character had the mind
like God absence so to be in the image
and likeness of God simply means that
man acted like God how many people would
like to act like God if some of you
looking funny like wait what do you mean
by no no no I don't mean to be God I
simply mean to act to behave to to to
follow God's character yeah amen so man
was made in the image and likeness of
God meaning he had the character of God
or let me say this way he had the mind
of God his mind was holy pure righteous
that's the first thing I want you to
note the second thing I want you to know
is that there are two kingdoms in this
verse
how many kingdoms everyone - what are
those kingdoms the kingdom of men and
the kingdom of animals the animal
kingdom so when God made man in His
image he said you will have dominion
over the fowl of the air over the fish
of the sea and over everything that
creeps upon the earth but something
happened man sin yes Genesis chapter 3
verse 1 Genesis chapter 3 verse 1 the
Bible says now the serpent was more
subtle than any beast of the hold on
wait a minute what is the serpent here
hmm very interesting Satan works through
a serpent which the Bible says was a
beast to get Adam and Eve to disobey God
yeah yeah yeah no no no because we have
blank looks on your faces right now so
when God created Adam and Eve he had
given them dominion over the beasts and
I feel the need and so what happens is
Satan comes in through a serpent
to put doubt in the minds of Adam and
Eve are you with me and he puts doubt in
there in the Word of God now it's very
interesting it's a dragon in this story
is the dragon in this story
yeah does the dragon works through a
beast in this story do the Dragon and
the Beast turn Eve into a false
messenger
I'm ladies I'm sorry but you get there
forget about I just just just focus and
I want you to watch what's happening
here you have this threefold union that
basically comes to Adam and convinces
him to turn against God now what is a
deception over very listen very
carefully what were what were they told
you will be like God so would you say
that this would be a counterfeit of God
so a counterfeit of God yeah number one
and number two you will not surely die
so that is the teaching of the state of
the dead so the very first deception was
over a counterfeit dog and the state of
the day
a dragon a beast and a false messenger
when the Bible says that man sinned it's
very interesting because the Bible says
the Bible says that when God sees Adam
and Eve in the garden he says behold the
man has become as one of us now
I have recently discovered or come to
the understanding that that verse could
very well be a mistranslation
some translations actually read it in
the past tense meaning behold the man
who was as one of us remember when God
made man he made him in his image and in
his likeness meaning he was like God but
now when they have sinned they no longer
have the mind of God and what God is
basically saying here is behold what has
become of the one who was once like us
he is no longer like us when man was
made in the image of God he had dominion
over the beasts but now when man is no
longer in the image of God he now
reflects the image I want you to think
with me King they can go beast mode
somebody got that late but they got it
amen
Cain went be smoked meaning his
character the character of man who was
once in the image of God when they
stepped out of the image and likeness of
God they went beast mode think about the
flood were man acting more like these
yeah how many remember this story where
Joseph was sold by his brothers and
remember what they did they took his
coat and they dip it in blood
I remember the excuse they came up with
they said come let us tell our father
that some wild beast has devoured now
they thought they were lying
they were not lying
they were the beasts they were the ones
that how many follow what I'm saying
they were the beasts they were not lying
so I want you to begin to get this now
you remember Nebuchadnezzar give me what
happened to him he became a beast when
man decides to lift himself again
against God to do his own will what God
is saying is you have gone into beast
mode now now it becomes no wonder then
that when we get to the Book of Daniel
we see the kingdoms of men being
described as beasts a lion a lion
represents ferocity a bear it devours
much flesh a leopard its camouflage a
dragon it bruises and breaks in pieces
beloved I want you to understand that
when man is no longer reflecting the
image of God what happens to nations is
that they begin to reflect the images of
beasts understand what I'm saying
beloved because I'm gonna bring this
home a little bit closer to us do you
know any Christians
that are camouflaged that devour much
flesh you know feed on people hey did
you hear since it's all so beloved the
characteristics of these beasts are a
reflection of the characteristics of the
human heart that is not submitted to the
will of God beasts mold many of us in
here tonight
are in peace mode but I want you to
understand that that the end result of
the kingdoms of men becoming the
kingdoms of beasts the end result of man
giving over Dominion to the beasts is
this we go to the book of Revelation and
guess what we find we find three beasts
one from the sea give you some time one
from the earth one from the air the
dragon the Beast the false prophet
beloved listen to me this is the end
result of man not reflecting the image
and likeness of God let me talk to you
for a moment about two beasts in
particular and I want you to understand
something you see the Bible says that by
beholding we become changed so how do
you think The Devil's trying to get you
into beasts more by beholding beasts
okay
there are two beasts that are described
in the book of Revelation chapter 11 and
chapter 13 one of those beasts is called
the beast from the bottomless pits how
many of you familiar what that beast
represents that beast represents atheism
it is from the French Revolution I mean
you're familiar with that now yeah Bible
prophecy students French Revolution late
1700s this is described as the Beast
rising out of the bottomless pit now
what was particularly French Revolution
well the French Revolution very
interestingly very interesting the
French Revolution is where a term was
first introduced and that term listen
carefully is the term left and right
hold on guys those listen carefully
those who were against the King and
against the church sat on the left they
were they were what you might call you
know progressive they they were for you
know all kinds of different rights and
different things of this nature
but but one very important thing they
rejected the God of the Bible we want
nothing to do with God so that's how the
reign of terror came about and the whole
banishing of the Bible for a certain
period of time all this is that is what
happened in the French Revolution this
is the beast from the bottomless pit and
beloved let me tell you when we in the
church begin to the whole that beast and
the things about that beast and we begin
to admire that beast what begins to
happen is a church begins to become
affected let me say infected but there
is another beast this one is found in
Revelation 13 this beast has the horns
of a lamb but speaks like a dragon that
was another revolution that took place
just about the same time and that
revolution was called the American
Revolution we're talking about the
United States of America
horns of a land you look like a lamb but
when you go to be petted you run like a
dragon do you know people who look like
lambs coming to church you're like this
habit and they roar at you raw and it
scares you to death doesn't it because
you expect a lamb to bahaha piranhas but
they don't Baha they roar and you're
like whoa if that's what a Christian is
what I don't want anything to do with it
beloved many of us are walking around
with the horns of a lamb but speaking
like a dragon and beloved listen to me
in our nation today our nation is
reflecting more and more honor I'm gonna
say something that might be you know
might become listen to me do you know
that the reason that our pioneers taught
that America was the beast with the
horns of a lamb and spake of the dragon
do you know that the reason they taught
that was because of one reason and that
reason was slavery absolutely you go
check it out in the writings of sister
white you go check it out in the
writings of brother white of your eyes
Smith they all agreed that any nation
that could claim Christianity and yet
sell the souls of men was a beast that
looked like a lamb but spoke like a
dragon but over the point is this that
beast is still alive today and
Christianity in America is turning many
people off from God you see the devil
wears two masks let me say this the
devil uses two beasts he doesn't care
which beast you should choose your Beast
oh you like this piece better choose
your Beast because what happens is that
by beholding the Beast we become like
the Beast and beloved what I'm trying to
tell you tonight is that you and I as
God's people need to stop beholding
beasts and start looking to Jesus
because by beholding beloved we be karma
changed
listen America is beautiful and praise
God but listen carefully guys
it was hyper nationalism that put Jesus
to death did you catch what I just said
it is expedient for us that one man
perished in order to save our nation but
I would listen to me Jesus Christ must
be our first and foremost love amen
in fact while there was bad news that
Satan has an image to the Beast there
was good news that there is an image of
God and the image of God is Jesus Christ
and so beloved listen to me God sent his
son who is his Express image into the
world so that we could behold him and be
changed from beasts back into the image
of God he knew he was coming to a world
of beasts he was born in a manger among
animals he was born in a manger of it
almost as if he was saying look I know
I'm coming to a world of beasts but I
love these beasts I came to die for
these people who aren't acting like
animals who are acting out of my
character I came to die that they might
have another chance to reflect the image
of God not the image of the beast by
beholding beloved we become what changed
you see Jesus Christ was beast proof how
many of you would like to be beast proof
beloved you have to be beast proof
because listen Jesus wants you to master
the Beast right here if you can't master
the Beast right here forget about the
Beast of Revelation 13 because you are
already set up for failure
so our main battle right now is to slay
the Beast within the image of the beast
right here and how do we do that how
does God move us from the mind of the
Beast to the mind of Christ the Bible
says let this one mind be in you which
was also in Christ Jesus not that I want
you to check this out okay we're about
to worry about to who Lord give me the
time listen when God made man he made
him in His image and his likeness but he
also made him as a temple as of what
everyone know you not that you are the
one temple of the Holy Ghost not the
Spirit of God dwells in you so why was
man reflective of the image of God
because man was made a temple and inside
the temple was the law of God is that
right in the Old Testament the actual
temple that was built the law of God was
inside the temple the law of God was
inside the temple amen the law of God
was inside that
Oh bright like I said the law of God was
inside the temple and when the law of
God was inside the temple man reflected
His image but what happened is that sin
broke the law sin broke the temple and
so Jesus says I'm gonna get when when
Jesus came to this world the Bible says
of him that he was the sanctuary yes
that means that the temple is a template
of Jesus the temple is a template of
Jesus meaning if the mind of Christ is
to be in us then what God is trying to
show us in the temple is this is how you
get the mind of Christ yeah you're on
everything you know something put out
there let this mind be in you which was
also in Christ Jesus and we have no idea
what that means because we don't address
it practically so beloved listen to me
listen carefully what was in the temple
the altar of sacrifice what else the
Laver what else the candlestick the
table of showbread the altar of incense
what else the Ark of the Covenant listen
to me beloved it is in the sanctuary
that beasts were slain
it was in the sanctuary that beast was
how many of you would like your beefs to
be flame guess where you gotta go you
gotta go to the sanctuary because it's
in the sanctuary beloved at the altar of
sacrifice where the where the beast was
slain and that the Laver where you wear
your sins are washed away and the table
of showbread where were you begin to
focus on the Word of God instead of
focusing on your own word and your own
will and the altar of incense where you
learn how to pray instead of learning
how to pray and the candlestick where
you begin to have passion for the word
of God and and you have vision for God's
vision and the Ark of the Covenant where
the law of love becomes written on your
mind
and so what God is saying is that as you
go through the sanctuary
I will remake you into my image and into
my likeness these articles of furniture
represents a very mind of Christ the
altar of sacrifice points to his
humility in his death the Laver points
to his forgiveness the the table of
showbread points to his truth the altar
of incense points to his focus that will
keep him in perfect peace whose mind is
what stayed on the the candlestick to
his vision and the law of God to his
love in other words the sanctuary is a
picture of the mind of Christ and every
time you focus on altar sacrifice
man someone cursed me out today and I
want to do this but Lord altar sacrifice
all throw sacrifice okay yeah you're
learning how to change your thoughts by
way you ever heard of neuroplasticity
how you can create new pathways in your
mind the sanctuary beloved is God's
neuroplasticity program where as you
learn to think through these articles of
furniture it actually changes the way
you
and you stop thinking in beastmode and
you start thinking in christ mode and
beloved when you do this over and over
again when you do this continually when
you do this tamid anybody know what the
word Tommy means
yeah it's that prophetic word that we
use in Daniel to talk about the articles
of furniture in the sanctuary how the
priest would operate these articles
daily listen to me beloved these
articles of furniture must be operating
daily in our minds because when we learn
to make them operate daily what begins
to happen is it begins to be written
Jana feeling me mad it is now written in
your mind and something called
automaticity takes place which is when
you do something so much it becomes
automatic it becomes second nature you
don't even think about it anymore it is
reflex how many of you would like divine
reflexes beloved start thinking through
the sanctuary because God's Way beloved
is where in the sanctuary and now it's
time for me to begin my sermon this is
the main part don't worry I'm not
keeping you for the 16 minutes I think I
can do this in 16 minutes guys okay why
do we need the mind of Christ why do we
need the mind of Christ because the mind
of Christ is beast proof is what
everyone it's beast proof meaning in
order for me to not be deceived by these
beasts at the end of time I must have
them the mind of Christ so where can I
use sealed you know
sealed so written here that it becomes
that there is no way for the devil can
put doubt in my mind remember what he
did with Eve without him he put doubt in
their minds now now come with me
Revelation chapter 16 this is the study
part of our message we will try to
complete it in the remaining 15 minutes
Revelation chapter 16 Revelation chapter
16 and verse 13 Revelation 16 and verse
13 the Bible says here
Revelation chapter 16 and verse 13 and I
saw three unclean spirits like what
frogs come out of the mouth of the Lu
Dragon and out of the mouth of the who
beasts and out of the mouth of the false
prophet for they are the spirits of lot
devils working what everyone miracles
which go forth unto the kings of the
earth and of the whole world to gather
them to the Battle of the great day of
God Almighty so here you have three
unclean spirits coming out of the mouth
of the Beast the dragon and the false
messenger did you hear what I said
if we were to translate this this would
be the beast from the sea the beast from
the earth and the dragon the Prince of
the air amen
so the question is how is it that these
beasts are going to attempt to try to
deceive God's people well let me explain
why does the Bible use frogs in this
verse three unclean spirits like frogs
listen carefully how many of you
remember where else frogs who are used
in the Bible you know Egypt right it's a
story of Egypt and you remember when
when Moses is performing these miracles
he turns water into wine into blood and
then the age of the Egyptian magicians
did what they counterfeited it and then
he threw it on his rod and turned to a
serpent and the Egyptian magicians what
do they do they counterfeited it and
then he brought up four frogs and one of
the Egyptian magicians do they
counterfeited it listen carefully guys
it was the last counterfeit they could
do it was the final counterfeit that
they could pull off so the reason the
book of Revelation is using these these
are frogs to represent these unclean
spirits that go out to perform miracles
is that it's trying to tell us that this
is going to be Satan's final deception
and this is the deception that has to
deal with counterfeiting with what
everyone
counterfeiting how many of you remember
the parable of the five the ten virgins
500 wise and five were foolish they all
slept listen guys they all slept and
something woke them up what was it that
woke them up when did they wake up let
me ask that when did they wake up
midnight midnight is the darkest hour of
the night so what the Bible is telling
us here is that there is going to be an
event an event that is that may be
described as the time of trouble such as
never was it is the darkest hour of
Earth's history something that that
wakes up both the wise and the foolish
virgins and you've got to follow this
because I need you to come with me to
Daniel chapter 12 verse 1 and 2 we're
going back to the Book of Daniel and you
guys knows what no what happens there
Daniel 12:1 and 2 the Bible says in at
that time shall Michael stand up the
Great Prince was standing for the
children of his people and there will be
a time of what trouble such as never was
and then it goes on to speak about the
resurrection now Michaels standing up
what does that signify what's about to
happen
Jesus is about to come and when he comes
what happens to the day they are raised
again to life amen so Jesus comes and
the dead are raised amen
so what leads to Daniel 12:1 and 2 well
the answer is Daniel 11 verse 40 come
there with me Daniel 11 verse 40 Daniel
chapter 11 verse 40 and and I want you
to notice what the Bible says here
Daniel chapter 11 verse 40 the Bible
says here we go the Bible says and at
the time of the end shall the King of
the South push at him now let me just
pause right here I know I'm juicing a
lot of this down for you but just
salvation and signs and symbols is about
to release our Daniel study so if I'm
going too fast here just look out for it
in a few weeks and months a
plug plug plug and see okay all right so
the King of the South in this particular
verse represents atheism it represents
agnosticism and and you know that that
is very heavy in the world today right
there are a lot of people who don't
believe in God and bla bla bla
right but notice what happens to the
king of the south the Bible says
continues to say in verse 40 and the
king of the top at the time of the end
the King of the South shall push out him
and the king of the north shall come
against him like a whirlwind with
chariots and with horsemen and with many
ships so the Bible's telling us here
that the king of the north is going to
end up defeating the king of the south
so the question is who is the king of
the north and many of us believe we know
who he is it's the same power as the
little horn but beloved it's a little
bit more complicated than that because I
need you to see something here how does
the king of the north come against the
king of the south to defeat him with
what chariots ships whirlwind horsemen
right do you know that there's another
verse in the Bible almost identical to
this come Isaiah chapter 65 and I'm just
gonna read it in your hearing Isaiah 65
verse 15 check this out guys for behold
the Lord will come with fire and with
his chariots like a whirlwind stop stop
how's the Lord coming with chariots and
what and fire and a whirlwind does that
seem similar to this king of the north
how he comes LaNasa question what do you
think is the only thing that can defeat
atheism like totally just wipe it out
for an atheist seeing is believing
y'all are now catching me now for an
atheist
seeing is believing now I want you to
notice I'm here because in Isaiah
chapter 14 do you know how Lucifer
wanted to sit on the sides of the north
deny on the book of psalms the Bible
says beautiful for situation is Mars
ayan the city of the great king
on the sides of the north let me ask you
who is the true king of the north Jesus
amen
so who is this other king of the north
that comes like a whirlwind with
chariots and fire and basically wipes
out atheism
it is the counterfeit coming of Satan
himself beloved please listen to me the
papacy is to Satan what John the Baptist
was to Jesus see as Adventist we look
hard do you see what the papers they did
today
they sneezed the end of NIP below and
those are please I'm not me I'm just
trying to tell you that for many of us
our eyes are in the wrong place our eyes
are in the wrong place beloved with the
enemy when he could listen there was no
announcement when Satan appears see many
of us as Adventists have our own version
of the rapture when I was out in the
world I used to believe hey you know
what I heard about this rapture thing if
I see the rapture happen and people
disappear I know that I'll have seven
years and I'll get it to get it in we
have our own version it's sunday long
imma be in the clouds doing my thing and
and and I know what my parents and
everyone else is said about them enough
and I don't see a funding on your rising
but if I see Congress you know how long
they take to do anything if I see them
beginning to talk about Sunday know that
I'll praise Him praise Jesus then I'll
get ready but beloved listen to me when
Satan comes there is no announcements
and if you read great controversy she
tells us that it is in his assumed
disguise that he commands all to keep
the counterfeit Sabbath listen to me
No nothing in this world will bring the
whole world together
X
the miracle it will take a miracle for
atheist and radical Islam and Christian
it'll take a miracle for the whole world
to come together and that miracle is the
appearing of Jesus Christ the a
counterfeit appearing of Jesus Christ
now now now watch this guys because I
know what you are thinking I'm okay why
because when Jesus comes his feet don't
touch the ground yes I got it
the enemy won't catch me let me share
something with you when Jesus comes
again what also happens there's a
resurrection of the what of the day I
want you to think about this guys think
about Satan appearing not only does he
appear but he appears with the dead
now you got profit saying yeah
adventists you guys were wrong oh by the
way hold on remember when Jesus comes
again what is he about to set up the
Millennium the 1,000 years and in the
Millennium judgment is given to the
Saints yeah are you catching this listen
to me please let me say it again when
when Jesus comes judgment is given to
the Saints but this happens where in
heaven so when the counterfeit occurs
guess what he's gonna say
I'm giving judgment to my Saints and
your job is to judge the wicked and
guess who the wicked are going to be
by the way from one new moon to another
and from one Sabbath to another all
flesh is to come before me and worship
and if you don't you are being
disobedient to my theocracy to my
kingdom but I listen to me I know what
you're thinking right now
hey if I know the truth and I'll be okay
do you know that John the Revelator how
many of you would like what you know I
think John the Revelator is on good
Christian character John the Revelator
saw an angel in heaven
and Angel and Angel not Jesus and angel
and John the Revelator was so
overwhelmed by the glory of this angel
and the angel said stop what are you
doing now how many John the Revelator is
do we have out here tonight he didn't do
it once he did it twice beloved if you
think oh Jesus feet don't touch the
ground it's gonna be enough to keep you
you have to understand if the image of
the Beast has any piece of your heart
when the Beast comes you will be
attracted to it because like attracts
like beloved the five foolish virgins
are unprepared why because listen to me
you don't prepare for a marathon on the
day of the marathon and that's what many
of us are doing well when we see things
we're gonna happen then we'll get ready
then we'll make it right
no beloved that's the wrong approach you
gotta get ready now you need a mind of
Christ now you need to start studying
your Bible now you need to start acting
like Jesus now stop cursing people out
in church stop stop don't do it in a
stop don't claim it in the name of Jesus
stop having enemies
stop acting like a beast like a dragon
that looks like a lamb but it's speaking
like the devil beloved it is not good
enough to claim that you know Bible
prophecy and you understand what's going
to happen and yet your character has not
been transformed act like Jesus think
like Jesus talk like Jesus because
beloved the time is coming where he that
is filthy will have to be filthy still
and he that his righteous will be
righteous still and if you have not
prepared for the marathon before the
marathon hit you will be like those five
foolish virgins who will open mock
saying open up to us open up to us and
Jesus will say I never knew you depart
from me so I have one minute to make an
appeal my appeal is very simple tonight
Lord I need to slay this beast I need to
slay this beast
I need this beast out of my heart and I
need to go into your sanctuary it is a
changing room so Lord I'm inviting you
I'm inviting you into my heart now slay
this beast because if I don't beat the
beast here I will have no chance against
the Beast there he will create enough
doubt in my mind through what I see that
I will doubt the word just like he was
able to create doubt in the minds of
Adam and Eve help my mind to be stayed
on you if that's your desire I'm gonna
invite you to just come to the front
we're gonna have a special prayer
cameras will roll out but you don't
worry about that you're coming to the
front right now you're saying what I
need to slay this beast I need to slay
this beast change my heart God
change my heart I don't want to reflect
the image of the beast I want to reflect
the image of God
but ever the time for church games is
over
the time for appearing like a lamb and
and not acting like a lamb it's over
we are living at the very end of time
[Music]
and I want you to remember this Jonah
I'm sorry Noah
[Music]